

# Profile

I work as a software developer and I have a passion for teaching programming and delivering information in the simplest and best way possible.

I studied computer engineering at 19 May University in Samsun, Turkey.

I helped hundreds of students to learn how to code and change their lives by becoming mobile app developers.

My first experience in programming in action was in 2008 when I wanted to create my own application and make profits by selling it in the labor market.

Since then, I've made hundreds of apps.

# Employment History

### Freelancer Developer

November 2008 — Present

#### Youtuber

November 2020 — Present

Code With Ammar

# **Mobile Apps Development instructor**

January 2020 — Present

Udemy

## Education

Computer Engineering Bachelor Degree, 19 Mayis Universitesi,-Samsun-Turkey

November 2015 — November 2019

Bachelor's degree in Software Engineering

# ■ References

References available upon request

#### **Details**

+905549910000

i5549910000@gmail.com

### Links

Youtube Channel

Udemy

Facebook

Twiter

Web Site

### Skills

Effective Time Management

Communication Skills

Microsoft Office

Node.js

HTML & CSS

PHP

MySQL

Java

Firebase

Swift

Flutter

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Premiere Pro

Adobe After Effects

Final Cut Pro

**Editing Video** 

### Languages

English

Turkish

Arabic